

# Alexander Lamm

## **Software Developer**

https://github.com/misterlamm - alexlammseven@gmail.com - https://www.linkedin.com/in/alex-lamm-416078149/ - https://misterlamm.github.io/portfolio

# Qualifications Summary

Creatively minded, budding full-stack software developer. Gained teamworking/building skills through previous work/internship and programming bootcamp experience. Worked on and completed dozens of projects through courses and on my own efforts (many more to come), including a marine debris tracking app. On a journey to become a programming Swiss-army knife that can use whatever tool (language, library, etc.) is necessary to accomplish a project.

### **Skills**

#### Front-end Programming

JavaScript HTML/CSS

#### **Back-end Programming**

Java Node

postgresSQL

MS SQL

## **Work History**

NORTH STAR DESTINATION STRATEGIES - Nashville, TN

N 2016 - 2016

Intern

Performed tasks such as data entry, client contact list building using Excel, creating and editing PowerPoint presentations, sitting in on calls with clients and taking notes, organizing promotional materials from clients, and offering creative assistance as needed.

RAISING CANE'S CHICKEN- Charleston, SC

2010 - 2013

**Crew Member** 

Customer service, food preparation, and conflict resolution.

#### Education

THE IRON YARD - Charleston, SC

2017 - 2017

Front-end & Back-end software Development (studied)

BELMONT UNIVERSITY - Nashville, TN

2014 - 2016

Bachelor Business Administration (BBA) Music Business

MIDDLE TENNESSEE STATE UNIVERSITY - Murfreesboro, TN 2011 - 2014

Music Business (studied)